{
    "subject": "resource/Sakyo_Komatsu",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Japan_Sinks",
    "human_readable": "Sakyo Komatsu's notable work is Japan Sinks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9505383968353271,
            "question": "Has Sakyo Komatsu written any other notable works besides 'Japan Sinks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7796322107315063,
            "question": "Which disaster scenario is depicted in Sakyo Komatsu's famous work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5866507291793823,
            "question": "What book is considered a notable work by Sakyo Komatsu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5829436779022217,
            "question": "What is Sakyo Komatsu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4249308407306671,
            "question": "What impact did 'Japan Sinks' have on Japanese culture and literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3649248480796814,
            "question": "How is 'Japan Sinks' generally perceived by readers and critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31099188327789307,
            "question": "Are there any adaptations of 'Japan Sinks' in other media formats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23905621469020844,
            "question": "Is there a specific event or real-world concern that influenced Sakyo Komatsu's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23356248438358307,
            "question": "Name a prominent Japanese author known for disaster fiction."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17978186905384064,
            "question": "What genre does Sakyo Komatsu primarily write in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sakyo Komatsu's notable work is Japan Sinks.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8412_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a prominent Japanese author known for disaster fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8412_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific event or real-world concern that influenced Sakyo Komatsu's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8412_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any adaptations of 'Japan Sinks' in other media formats?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8412_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8412_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Sakyo Komatsu's notable work is Japan Sinks.\" The documents mention that Japan Sinks was authored by Sakyo Komatsu and provides details about its publication, awards won, and cultural impact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}